<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IIITKota</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="contact">Contacts</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faculty">Faculty</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newsfeed">NewsFeed</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="mytext">Members of university administration (e.g., department chairs, deans, vice presidents, presidents, and librarians) are often also faculty members, in many cases beginning (and remaining) as professors. In some universities, the distinction between \'academic faculty\' and \'administrative faculty\' is made explicit by the former being contracted for nine months per year, meaning that they can devote their time to research (and possibly be absent from the campus) during the summer months, while the latter are contracted for twelve months per year. These two types of faculty status are sometimes known as \'nine-month faculty\' and \'twelve-month faculty\'. Faculty who are paid a nine-month salary are typically allowed to seek external funds from grant agencies to partially or fully support their research activities during the summer months.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery__images">Gallery_Images</string>

    <string name="title_activity_gallery__detailed_view">Gallery_DetailedView</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="dispensary">"Dispensary"</string>
    <string name="aurobindo">"Aurobindo Hostel"</string>
    <string name="Basketball">"Basketball Court"</string>
    <string name="prabha">"Prabha Bhavan"</string>
    <string name="gargi">"Gargi Hostel"</string>
    <string name="maingate">"MNIT Main Gate"</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">"AIzaSyDbb_gtVij1xgY0pXgPtMrNiM4pdMb77NE"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">About Us</string>

    <!--About Us Module-->
    <string name="about_iiitk">IIIT Kota is a joint venture of the Ministry of Human Resource Development,
        Government of India, Rajasthan Government with Industries in Public-Private Partnership model.</string>
    <string name="mission">To create technical manpower for meeting the current and future demands of industry:
        To recognize education and research in close interactionwith industry with emphasis on the development
        of leadership qualities in the young menand women entering the portals of the Institute with sensitivity
        to social development andeye for opportunities for growth in the international perspective</string>
    <string name="vision">To create a center for imparting technical education of international standards and conduct research at the cutting edge of
        technology to meet the current and future challenges of technological development.</string>
</resources>
